[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All these entities are located around the Black Sea except for one. Name the exception.", "correct_answer": "Ural mountains", "incorrect_answers": ["Balkan peninsula", "Caucasus mountains", "Anatolia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This astronaut claimed he was the first man to wet his pants on the moon.", "correct_answer": "Buzz Aldrin", "incorrect_answers": ["Gus Grissom", "Neil Armstrong", "Chuck Rollands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Shaun of the Dead, what is the main characters weapon of choice?", "correct_answer": "a Cricket bat", "incorrect_answers": ["an Axe", "a Baseball bat", "a Knife"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actress plays the prostitute in St. Elmos Fire, who propositions Kevin outside of the apartment he shares with Kirby?", "correct_answer": "Anna Maria Horsford", "incorrect_answers": ["Janet DuBois", "Marla Gibbs", "Alaina Reed Hall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The protagonist of this slasher movie carries a chainsaw and wears a mask with holes all around?", "correct_answer": "Friday the 13th", "incorrect_answers": ["Halloween", "Scream", "Nightmare on Elmstreet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the smallest elephant subspecies on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Sumatran Elephant", "incorrect_answers": ["Forest Elephant", "Indian Elephant", "Sri Lankan Elephant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Glenwood Springs, Colorado was known for its hot springs and hospital. What famous outlaw and gun slinger expired from Tuberculosis there?", "correct_answer": "Doc Holliday", "incorrect_answers": ["Billy The Kid", "Jesse James", "Wyatt Earp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The region of Pomerania (ger.: Pomern, pol.: Pomorze) is located in north Germany and Poland. Which river divides the region into two parts?", "correct_answer": "Oder (Odra)", "incorrect_answers": ["Vistula", "Danube", "Elbe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what century did the great Greek philosopher Socrates live?", "correct_answer": "5th century BC", "incorrect_answers": ["10th century BC", "2nd century BC", "8th century BC"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ernest Vincent Wright wrote a book, called Gadsby, which consisted of 50,000 words, none of which contained this letter.", "correct_answer": "E", "incorrect_answers": ["O", "I", "A"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the director of the 1964 comedy movie Dr. Strangelove or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb?", "correct_answer": "Stanley Kubrick", "incorrect_answers": ["Steven Spielberg", "Alfred Hitchcock", "Martin Scorsese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the title of this 1990 film, starring Tom Hanks: ....Versus the Volcano.", "correct_answer": "Joe", "incorrect_answers": ["Gus", "Pat", "Tom"]}]